https://rinnai.co.nz/page/20/privacy

Warranty
Why Rinnai?
Rinnai INFINITY® N-Series
Continuous hot water solutions for residential and commercial applications
Rinnai INFINITY® A-Series
Continuous hot water solutions for residential applications
Rinnai INFINITY® HD
Continuous hot water solutions for residential and commercial applications
Mains Pressure Hot Water Cylinders
Great shower pressure, solar and heat pump capable, and a 10 year warranty
Low Pressure Hot Water Cylinders
Copper or upgrade to a stainless steel for a 10 year warranty
Mains Pressure Coiled Hot Water Cylinders
Connect to solar or wetback to save money on your power bill
Central Heating
Gas ducted home heating and add-on cooling for your whole home
Energysavers
Flued heaters that maintain air quality for a healthy breathing environment
Warranty
Why Rinnai?
Careers
Product Registration
Contact
Phone:+64 9 257 3800Freephone:0800 746 624Fax:+64 9 257 3899Email:info@rinnai.co.nz
Postal Address:PO, Box 53177Auckland AirportAuckland 2150Physical Address:105 Pavilion DriveMangereAuckland
Showroom105 Pavilion DrMangereAuckland 2150*Please note that Rinnai New Zealand does not sell direct to the public.Opening HoursMonday to Friday: 8:30am - 4:30pm
Enquire Now
Please enter your name
Please enter your email address
Please enter your phone number
Please enter a message
Subscribe to mailing list
Privacy
Legal
Privacy
Cookie Policy
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This Privacy Statement governs the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data by us and has been prepared in accordance with our obligations and your rights set out in the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993. We reserve the right to modify or amend this Privacy Statement at any time and for any reason. By using this website ("Site") you consent to our use of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Statement (as amended from time to time).
This Privacy Statement explains:
What kind of personal data we collect
Where we collect personal data from
How we use personal data
How you can access/amend your personal data
How long we hold personal data
Who you can contact for further information.
What kind of personal data we collect
We collect only the personal data you give us (including your name, email address, residential address and contact telephone numbers). We may also keep a record of any products and services that you receive from us.
Where we collect personal data from
We collect personal data from the following sources:
By you contacting us enquiring about information on us or our servcies or anything on this Site
Directly from you when you ask us to supply you with products or services in connection with this Site
Indirectly through your use of this Site and the servcies and functionality offered through it.
How we use personal data
We use your personal data for the following purposes:
Replying to your queries
Providing you with information about us and our products and services
Providing you with products and services in relation to this Site
Complying with relevant legislation and regulations
Any specific purpose which we notify you at the time personal data is collected
Rinnai may pass your personal information to relevant external parties.
How we store personal data
We store personal data electronically and in paper form. The personal data is kept safe and secure using generally accepted standardsof security.
How you can access/amend your personal dataYou may access your personal data we hold by emailing us at info@rinnai.co.nz. We will provide you with a copy of the personal datawe keep about you.
You may request that the personal data we hold about you be corrected by emailing us at info@rinnai.co.nz. If we agree that your personal data is to be corrected we will provide you with an amended record of your personal data.
We will keep your personal data only for as long as necessary to achieve the purpose we collected it for.
Who you can contact for further information
Privacy contact: Managing Director
Email address: info@rinnai.co.nz
Address: 105 Pavilion Drive, Airport Oaks, Mangere
Postal Address: PO Box 53177, Auckland Airport, Auckland 2150
Support/Need Help?
